//  Element buff descriptions.

#_index
#_begin

1  "Stun
Unable to perform any actions"
2  "Sleep
Unable to perform any actions until attacked"
3  "Slow
Reduced speed"
4  "Physical Reflect
Physical melee damage is returned to the attacker"
5  "Plume Shield
Part of damage taken from MP instead of HP"
6  "Flame Shield
Increased Fire Resistance and accelerated HP recovery"
7  "Ice Shield
Increased Water Resistance and accelerated MP recovery"
8  "Frozen
Unable to move"
9  "Total Intervention
Can't use any attacks or skills."
10  "SEDUCE targeted monster alter to passive attack mode
"
11  "Rock Shield 
Increased Earth Resistance and Physical Defense"
12  "Thunder
Taking Metal damage over time"
13  "Poison
Taking Wood damage over time"
14  "Burn
Taking Fire damage over time"
15  "Sandstorm
Taking Earth damage over time"
16  "Manaleak
MP draining over time"
17  "Bleed
Taking physical damage over time"
18  "Weaken
Decreased physical defense"
19  "Distract
Decreased magic defense"
20  "Fright
Decreased physical attack"
21  "Curse
Increased damage taken"
22  "Slow
Decreased attack rate"
23  "Stupefy
Channeling slowed"
24  "Blind
Decreased accuracy
"
25  "Daze
Decreased evasion
"
26  "Increased HP recovery"
27  "Increased MP recovery"
28  "Maximum HP increased"
29  "Maximum MP increased"
30  "Fortified Armor
Increased physical defense"
31  "Concentrate
Increased magic defense"
32  "Sharpen
Increased physical attack"
33  "Quicken
Increased attack rate"
34  "Dodge
Increased evasion"
35  "Bless
Decreased damage taken"
36  "Nimble
Increased accuracy"
37  "Focus
Accelerated channeling"
38  "Water damage added to attack"
39  "Fire damage added to attack"
40  "Wood damage added to attack"
41  "Recovering HP"
42  "Recovering MP"
43  "Muddle
Decreased magic attack"
44  "Increased movement speed"
45  "Maximum HP decreased"
46  "Intuition
Increased magic attack"
47  "Untamed Transform"
48  "Metal resistance increased"
49  "Wood resistance increased"
50  "Water resistance increased"
51  "Fire resistance increased"
52  "Earth resistance increased"
53  "Metal resistance decreased"
54  "Wood resistance decreased"
55  "Water resistance decreased"
56  "Fire resistance decreased"
57  "Earth resistance decreased"
58  "Merbreath
Breathe and use skills while underwater"
59  "Essential Sutra
Skills do not require chanelling"
60  "Spark Eruption
All stats improved"
61  "Alter Marrow Physical
Decreased magic defense, increased physical defense."
62  "Alter Marrow Magical
Decreased physical defense, increased magic defense."
63  "Bestial Rage
Gain Chi while being attacked"
64  "Fortified Armor
Increased physical defense"
65  "Aura of the Golden Bell
Increased physical defense"
66  "Strength of the Titans
Increased physical attack"
67  "Blood Bath
Decreased MAX HP, increased accuracy"
68  "Intuition
Increased magic attack"
69  "Winged Shell
Reduced damage taken, MP recovery increased"
70  "Blazing Arrow
Adds Fire damage to attack"
71  "Stormrage Eagleon
Taking Metal damage over time, speed decreased"
72  "Immune to movement debuffs"
73  "Taking Water damage over time"
74  "Increased Critical Hit rate"
75  "Venomancer Transform"
76  "Invincible"
77  "Bramble Hood
Damage taken greatly reduced, physical damage reflected"
78  "Soul Degeneration
HP and MP recovery stopped"
79  "Amplify Damage
Damage taken increased"
80  "Crush Vigor
Lose Chi when attacked"
81  "Summer Sprint
Movement speed increased"
82  "Riding speed increased"
83  "Physical attack increased"
84  "Concentration
Increase concentration points to avoid being disturbed while casting spells.
Target becomes immune to seal. "
85  "Stimulation
A person being stimulated will never fall asleep.
Target beomes immune to Hypnosis."
86  "Freedom
With a free heart, you will never be slowed or freezed.
Target becomes immune to slow or Stun."
87  "Fortitude
Target becomes immune to proportionally lose health point.
A fortitudinous person will never be defeated completely."
88  "Holiness
Target becomes immune to all negative statuses."
89  "Petrifaction
Target becomes immune to physical damage."
90  "Immune to Fire
Target becomes immue to Fire damage."
91  "Immune to Water
Target becomes immue to Water damage."
92  "Immune to Metal
Target becomes immune to Metal damage."
93  "Immune to Wood
Target becomes immune to Wood damage."
94  "Immune to Earth
Target becomes immune to Earth damage."
95  "Immune to Elements
Target becomes immune to all Elemental damage."
96  "Rampage
Target becomes immune to all status."
97  "Subaqueous Deceleration
Slow down in the water."
98  "Subaqueous Acceleration
Speed up in the water."
99  "Aerial Deceleration
Slow down in the air."
100  "Aerial Acceleration
Speed up in the air."
101  "Land Deceleration
Slow down on land."
102  "Explosion
Recover Chi constantly."
103  "Exhaust
Lose Chi constantly."
104  "Power of Fairy
Constantly increase genie's strength in certain period of time."
105  "Dexterity of Fairy
Constantly increase genie's dexterity in certain period of time."
106  "Air Blade
You released an Air Blade to the enemy,
You're under the protection of wind now.
Increase physical defense."
107  "Element Weakness
Increase a target's physical defense, but impairs the Elemental Resistance."
108  "Deep Poison
Increase damage on a target. This effect can be accumulated with other skills like Heaven's Flame."
109  "Rooting
Immobilize yourself, and reduce and reflect damage received."
110  "Guardians of Earth
Recover HP every 3 seconds. Reduce damage received but also reduces Physical and Magic attack."
111  "Frenzy
Reduce a target's Physical and Magic defense while increasing their attack level. "
112  "Blinding Sand
Reduced Accuracy and Magic cast speed."
113  "Longing for Home
Accelerate HP and MP recovery and movement speed."
114  "Oblivion
Reduce Water defense."
115  "Luck
Increase critical hit rate."
116  "Impact
Reduce Physical defense."
117  "Flame
Reduce Fire Resistance."
118  "Anger in Heart
Reduce Physical and Magic attack speed."
119  "Kindling
Constant Fire damage."
120  "Burning Feet
Reduce Fire resistance and movement speed."
121  "Hard Wall
Absorb physical and magic damage, but reduce own move speed."
122  "Cutting Edge
Reduce Metal Resistance."
123  "Dancing Leaf
Reduce move speed and start to bleed."
124  "Scorch
Reduce defense and attack level
Slightly slow down move speed."
125  "Vacuum
Reduce release and move speed, and also received damage."
126  "Hardened Veins
Immune to Bleed status."
127  "Force Field
Absorbs physical damage."
128  "Magic Shell
Absorbs magic damage."
129  "Eye for an Eye
Reflects magic damage received."
130  "Wind Shield
Reduce damage received and increase Physical Attack speed and Evasion."
131  "Air Lock
Freeze a target and have a chance to Seal the target."
132  "Enclosure
Immune to Seal and Physical damage."
133  "Martial Trance
Immune to damage amplification."
134  "Freeze
Can't move."
135  "Attack Level increased"
136  "Attack Level decreased"
137  "Defense Level increased"
138  "Defense Level decreased"
139  "Recieves a Earth damage constantly."
140  "Total Intervention
Can't use any attacks or skills."
141  "Frozen
Unable to move"
142  "Bless
Decreased damage taken"
143  "Curse
Increased damage taken"
144  "Maximum HP increased"
145  "Sharpen
Increased physical attack"
146  "Intuition
Increased magic attack"
147  "Focus
Accelerated channeling"
148  "Increased movement speed"
149  "Stealth
Enter Stealth mode."
150  "Super Sight
Increased stealth detection"
151  "Bloodpaint
Recovers own HP by absorbing damage that you deal."
152  "Wolf Emblem
Increase own Critical hit damage."
153  "You have a chance to reduce the damage of incoming attacks."
154  "You have a chance to reduce the damage of incoming attacks."
155  "Blocks one attack that would deal lethal damage, and recovers some HP."
156  "Soul of Vengeance
Reflect damage to the attacker"
157  "Soul of Silence
Silence the attacker"
158  "Soul of Retaliation
Cast the attack's skill back to himself."
159  "Soul of Stunning
Stun the attacker"
160  "Increases the healing potency from spells and potions, and reduces the cooldown of healing charms."
161  "Decreases the healing potency from spells and potions, and increases the cooldown of healing charms."
162  "Receives damage while attacking or spellcasting"
163  "Interrupt
Each time the target cast a spell, it will be interrupted."
164  "Tide Form
Transforms you into a fish."
165  "Chill of the Deep
Reduces attack speed, increases attack level."
166  "Voodoo
Adjust the attack and defense level."
167  "Heart Shatter
Lowers Metal and Physical resistances and provides bonus damage to Metal and Physical skills."
168  "Mind Shatter
Lowers Wood and Water resistances and increases the critical strike rates for Wood and Water skills."
169  "Soul Shatter
Lowers Fire and Earth resistance and increase critical strike rate and damage of Fire and Earth skills"
170  "Northern Sky Waltz
Has a chance to apply Eye of the Northern Sky"
171  "Parchedblade Dance
Has a chance to apply Bloodletting"
172  "Soulsever Minuet
Has a chance to apply Spirit Bore"
173  "Eye of the Northern Sky
Staggering Strike deals additional damage, freezes the target, and lowers its Defense Level"
174  "Bloodletting
Stalagstrike deals additional damage ands tuns the target"
175  "Spirit Bore
Gemini Strike deals additional Metal damage and reduces the targets Attack and Defense Levels"
176  "Edged Blur
Deals Metal damage to nearby targets."
177  "Mist's Grasp
Continuous Wood damage when target's HP is lower than 60%."
178  "Falling Petals
Recovers HP continuously while being attacked."
179  "Verdant Shell
Increases Physical, Wood, and Water defenses."
180  "Slows the target"
181  "Energy of Beasts
Increases Physical Defense and Critical Hit Rate."
182  "Energy of Light
Increases Magic Defense and Magic Attack."
183  "Transference
Transfers Mana to the target."
184  "Shield of Flowers
Absorbs a portion of direct damage."
185  "Twin Flowers
Absorbs Damage and increases Defenses."
186  "Rapid Growth
Increased Channeling Rate and Magic Attack."
187  "Bloody Sun
Improves HP recovery speed over time"
188  "Sacrifice
Fire damage"
189  "Resurrect
Resurrect immediately after death"
190  "Take x2 damage from Absorb Soul attack"
191  "Enhanced Critical Strike"
192  "Duelist's Glee
Has a chance to apply Disarmed"
193  "Disarmed
Arme Nier deals additional damage and reduces the target's weapon damage."
194  "Weapon Disabled
Weapon temporarily disabled by a powerful attack"
195  "Hatred Increased
The caster's hatred increases greatly."
196  "Divine Bless
Doubles the skill damage to monsters"
197  "Awareness"
198  "Improves the MP recovery speed greatly"
199  "Will be teleported to you previous location after a short time"
200  "HP will revert to it's previous value after a short time"
201  "Unable to fly"
202  "Targets are selected at random"
203  "Aurora Blast"
204  "Arcane Defense"
205  "Reduces the chance of receiving critical hits"
206  "Increases the chance of receiving critical hits"
207  "Psionic Link
All damage taken will be redirected to the caster"
208  "A portion of healing received will be redirected to the caster."
209  "Death Link"
210  "HP will revert to it's previous value after a short time"
211  "Cannot be selected"
212  "Invigorate
Increases skill damage inflicted on monsters, and can be used with Divine Bless"
213  "An earth-based attack that charges up and deals damage later"
214  "Ice Prison"
215  "Spirit Fire
Reflect Physical damage"
216  "When attacked, may have a chance of stunning the attacker"
218  "Taking damage increases your Attack"
219  "Taking damage from enemies increase your Attack for a short time"
220  "Cornered Beast
Upon receiving a blow that would deal lethal damage, you will instead gain Health, Sparks, and remove negative status effects."
221  "A portion of a healing effect will be transferred to another player"
222  "Spoils of War"
223  "Attack Range Increased"
224  "Spirit Phalanx"
225  "Violet Dance"
226  "Sword Cyclone"
227  "Natural Synergy"
229  "Triggers when receiving melee damage.
Reduces melee damage taken for a short time."
230  "Attributes Increased"
231  "Increases HP and MP recovery speed when out of battle"
232  "Increases HP and MP recovery"
233  "All damage taken is increased. This effect can stack."
234  "You will not gain infany from engaging in PvP in this mode.
You do not drop items when killed.
You do not consume Guardian Scrolls.
You do not lose EXP on death."
235  "Increases Magic Resistance"
236  "Carrying the Flag
Movement speed is reduced. You cannot fly or use a Genie.
Flag will drop after being carried for 8 minutes."
237  "Defense Level reduced."
238  "Increases fighting ability"
239  "Critical Hit Rate increased."
240  "Defense Level and Slaying Level increased."
241  "Increases Health, Attack, and Defense Level "
242  "Increases Attack Level and Defense Level by 3"
243  "Increases character's Attack Level and Defense Level"
244  "Damage from players is reduced"
245  "Has a chance to cast a buff on yourself when attacking"
246  "Has a chance to cast a debuff on target when attacking."
247  "Immune to Physical damage"
248  "Immune to Metal damage"
249  "Immune to Wood damage"
250  "Immune to Water damage"
251  "Immune to Fire damage"
252  "Immune to Earth damage"
253  "Physical Reflect
Physical melee damage is returned to the attacker"
254  "Combat capability is improved."
255  "Paralyzed"
256  "Skill damage taken is increased."
257  "Increased chance to be critically hit."
258  "Specific skill''s Channelling Time is reduced."
259  "Specific skill's damage is increased."
260  "Glacial Embrace
Increases Water Resistance, accelerates MP recovery and constantly regenerates Chi."
261  "Pyroshell
Increases Fire Resistance, accelerates HP recovery and increases Critical Rate."
262  "Absorbs most damage and constantly regenerates Health."
263  "Increase the speed of flying
This effect can stack and refresh the lasting time"
264  "Spirit increased"
265  "Increase your Spirit, and reduce Critical Strike damage dealt to you."
266  "Lose health upon movement
Increase damage taken relative to distance moved."
267  "Dealt damage if distance moved is lower than the default value."
268  "Gain special abilities if distance moved is lower than the default value."
269  "Become invulnerable to interrupt skills while Shield is in effect."
270  "Suffer from a periodic paralysis effect"
271  "Internal Injury
Dealt additional bleed damage when health drops below 25%"
272  "Protection of Coldness
Reduces damage taken from normal attacks"
273  "Finishes the cooldown of Relentless Drift upon target's death"
274  "The specific skill has increased effect"
275  "Normal attacks cause additional damage"
276  "The specific skill has no cooldown"
277  "Destiny Hunter
Deals damage to foes. Missing the hit stuns you."
278  "Shadow Awakening
Increases attack rate, while decreasing damage taken from ranged attacks"
279  "Luna Awakening
Boost physical defense and movement speed, while enhancing dynamically cast spells."
280  "Dealt metal & water damage over time, stacks up to 5 times."
281  "Lunar Physique
Reduces damage taken and grants immunity to debuffs. Cannot be healed during Lunar Physique's duration."
282  "Increase direct damage inflicted on foes, can be used with Divine Bless."
283  "Reduces damage taken from critical attacks"
284  "Increases physical damage dealt"
285  "Increases spell damage dealt"
286  "Increases damage taken from skills"
288  "Cooldown before next Skill increased"
289  "Cannot be purged"
290  "Channeling distance to max effective distance increased"
291  "Phys. Def. and Mag. Def. increased"
292  "Metal Resistance decreased; cannot be dispelled"
293  "Water Resistance decreased; cannot be dispelled"
294  "Critical, Regeneration, and Chi"
295  "Escort Status
Cannot use Flyers or Mounts
Cannot use Sprint, Invisibility, or Teleportation
May use Rally Order, but unable to respond to Rally Orders or Summon Psychic skills"
296  "Increase the gain for XP, Spirit, and Vitae."
297  "Frostbite
Increases cooldown of Guardian Charms and Spirit Charms"
298  "Increases Physs. and Mag. ATK"
299  "Increases Phys. DEF"
300  "Increases Magic DEF"
301  "Increases Max HP"
302  "HP Regen"
303  "Reduces incoming damage"
304  "Attack Range Increased"
305  "Invincible"
306  "Metal DOT"
307  "Wood DOT"
308  "Water DOT"
309  "Fire DOT"
310  "Earth DOT"
311  "Physical Penetration increased"
312  "Magic Penetration increased"
313  "Attack Level increased"
314  "Defense Level increased"
315  "Damage increased"
316  "Drunken
Increases skill damage by 5% every stack.
After 10 stacks, deals great damage to players."
317  "Deceleration
After taking damage, speed will be reduced."
318  "Damage Reduction
Reduce damage taken by you."
319  "Martial Possession
After the direct damage skill is released, the next skill damage will be increased. Can be stacked."
320  "Magic Possession
Damage you deal and take is increased."
321  "Blessed Feather
Increases Max HP and restores HP."
322  "Vanish
Be in Stealth State over time."
323  "Ritual
Soulforce turns into Mag Attack."
324  "Soul Burst
Soulforce is reduced."
325  "Avatar of Blade
You size increases and are immune to all movement impairing effects. Your Attack Rate and Movement Speed are increased."
326  "Transfer damage to the pets."
327  "Death Curse
The moment you are killed, you transfer the damage to the enemies around you."
328  "The AOE damage you take from non-player units is reduced."
329  "The AOE damage you take from player units is reduced."
330  "The ranged direct damage you take from 8 meters away is reduced."
331  "Physical and Magic Defense are reduced."
332  "Physical and Magic Defense are reduced."
333  "The effect to restore HP from skills, Herbs and Health Charms is weakened."
334  "Increase Crit Strike and Critical damage."
335  "Reduce Channelling Time."
336  "Has a chance to evade the status of all attacking skills."
337  "Has a chance to evade the damage of all attacking skills."
338  "Divine Shield
Absorb damage for you."
339  "Turn the damage Divine Shield absorbs into losing Health over time."
340  "After a while, when you take damage and"
341  "HP is too low, all negative status effects will be removed,
and some HP is restored."
342  "Increases Attack, Defense and Max HP."
